{
    "subject": "resource/Slint",
    "predicate": "property/genre",
    "object": "resource/Post-rock",
    "human_readable": "The genre of Slint is Post-rock.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7254821062088013,
            "question": "What genre of music is Slint known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.706287682056427,
            "question": "If someone enjoys Post-rock music, would they likely enjoy Slint?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6628010272979736,
            "question": "To which genre does Slint belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6568130850791931,
            "question": "Name a genre that Slint is often categorized under."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6222479939460754,
            "question": "What musical style is associated with Slint?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5746626853942871,
            "question": "Give an example of a genre that Slint's music is similar to."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5014628767967224,
            "question": "What distinguishes Slint's sound from other genres?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4921206533908844,
            "question": "What type of music does Slint play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43651244044303894,
            "question": "How would you classify the music of Slint?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3544868528842926,
            "question": "What musical movement or trend is Slint often associated with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The genre of Slint is Post-rock.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7490_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you classify the music of Slint?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7490_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of music does Slint play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7490_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What distinguishes Slint's sound from other genres?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7490_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7490_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7490_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7490_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7490_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7490_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7490_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7490_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7490_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7490_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7490_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to the band Slint and their association with the post-rock genre. For instance, one document states, \"One of the defining bands of the post-rock genre was Slint,\" and another mentions that Slint is considered \"amongst the godfathers of Post-Rock/Math-rock.\" Therefore, the information supports the triple stating that the genre of Slint is Post-rock."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}